{
    "subject": "resource/Al_Jarreau",
    "predicate": "http://xmlns.com/foaf/0.1/name",
    "object": "Al Jarreau",
    "human_readable": "The name of Al Jarreau is Al Jarreau.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9766373634338379,
            "question": "What is the name of Al Jarreau?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9383995532989502,
            "question": "What is Al Jarreau known for?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8672332763671875,
            "question": "Why is it important to know the name of Al Jarreau?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7802073359489441,
            "question": "Is Al Jarreau a real person?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7399526834487915,
            "question": "How would you describe Al Jarreau?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6871277689933777,
            "question": "Where did you learn about Al Jarreau?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6800553798675537,
            "question": "What type of information do you have about Al Jarreau?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6635144948959351,
            "question": "Can you tell me more about Al Jarreau?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6521736979484558,
            "question": "Is there anything else you know about Al Jarreau?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.49759742617607117,
            "question": "Do you have any personal opinions about Al Jarreau?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The name of Al Jarreau is Al Jarreau.",
            "html": "dbpedia_9039_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Is there anything else you know about Al Jarreau?",
            "html": "dbpedia_9039_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Can you tell me more about Al Jarreau?",
            "html": "dbpedia_9039_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What type of information do you have about Al Jarreau?",
            "html": "dbpedia_9039_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9039_10.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9039_13.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9039_17.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9039_59.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9039_69.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9039_78.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9039_8.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9039_80.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9039_82.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9039_88.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n\n\n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "After evaluating the context information, I can tell you that:\n\n{'output': 'yes'}\n\nThe documents indeed mention \"Al Jarreau\" as his name multiple times."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```"
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "The Most Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}